girlgamesclub.com 2017-12-27

# Privacy Policy By Girl Games Club

This is the official privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for girlgamesclub.com ("Site," "we," "us," or "our"), an Internet website owned and operated by GCLUB Networks, Inc (GCLUB). This Privacy Policy governs only the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") collected by the Site. GCLUB is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online. 

**100% Privacy 100% safe!**  
girlgamesclub.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. girlgamesclub.com does not collect any personal information. The visitor log files on our webserver are disabled for speed and privacy reasons. 

**IP address and no logs**  
Your IP address is never used to gather broad demographic information and girl games club do not track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). There is no system on our server to store and process user information. We have no clue how many users are using our website and what our users are doing. Our webserver log files are disabled for speed, performance and privacy reasons. The current log level is 'emerg', meaning the server only make a log file in the event of a full server system crash. Our goal is to create a safe and free place to play girl games. Nothing less and nothing more then that! 

**Sharing Of Information**  
There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit girlgamesclub.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. You should visit cpmstar.com and google.com/adsense to learn more about their privacy policy and the cookies they might create. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The scripts that our third parties run are not located on our server:

Cpmstar Privacy Policy : [www.cpmstar.com](http://www.cpmstar.com/)  
Google Privacy Policy : [google.com/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)  
Google Cookie Policy : [google.com/policies/technologies/ads](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

* the external privacy policy of our third parties are not located on our server and may change in the future. 

**What are Cookies?**  
Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Our website is NOT using performance cookies and is NOT tracking your behaviour. However we are using third-party advertisers that might use cookies - please read the third party section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties. 

**Opt Out**  
You can opt out most advertisers [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note that the nai service will create cookies on your machine as well. 

**Liability**  
It is girlgamesclub.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, girlgamesclub.com will immediately disable and remove games in question. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Girl Games Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

This document is the sole statement of the Site's Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid. 

Girlgamesclub.com is a safe and free place for girl gamers!
